=Love For Two Lives=
= الحب لعمرين =
=Episode 26=
= الحلقة 26 =
Liangliang.
ليانجليانج.
(Your Majesty.)
(جلالة الملك).
(Maybe we should be parted for a while)
(ربما يجب أن نفترق لبعض الوقت)
(and think about our own future.)
(وفكر في مستقبلنا).
Liangliang, you are back.
Liangliang ، لقد عدت.
Grandma.
الجدة.
I haven't knitted with you for years.
أنا لم أحبك معك منذ سنوات.
I used to fool around when you knitted.
كنت أخدع عندما كنت محبوك.
Was I annoying?
هل كنت مزعجة؟
You were.
كنت.
Grandma.
الجدة.
But I
لكن أنا
always recall
أذكر دائما
when you were little.
عندما كنت صغيرا.
How is everything with Zheng?
كيف هو كل شيء مع تشنغ؟
Pretty good.
جيد جدا.
I'm not that easy to be fooled.
ليس من السهل أن ينخدعني.
You came back alone.
عدت وحدك.
There must be something wrong with you two.
يجب أن يكون هناك شيء خاطئ معكما.
You can tell me.
باستطاعتك اخباري.
Grandma.
الجدة.
If I tell you
إذا قلت لك
he's not from our world,
هو ليس من عالمنا ،
but a parallel world,
لكن عالم موازٍ ،
will you believe me?
هل تصدقني
I will.
أنا سوف.
Really?
هل حقا؟
I believe
أعتقد
anything you say.
أي شيء تقوله.
Come to grandma.
تعال إلى الجدة.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
He's a king in another world.
إنه ملك في عالم آخر.
The time crack opened in my house.
انفتح صدع الوقت في منزلي.
That's why we met each other.
لهذا التقينا ببعضنا البعض.
Well.
نحن سوف.
At first,
في البدايه،
we didn't get along.
لم نتفق.
But a lot of things
لكن الكثير من الأشياء
happened then,
حدث بعد ذلك ،
and we became friends.
وأصبحنا أصدقاء.
And then,
وثم،
we fell in love with each other.
وقعنا في حب بعضنا البعض.
I thought I could be with him forever.
اعتقدت أنني يمكن أن أكون معه إلى الأبد.
But the crack is closing in a few days.
لكن الكراك ينغلق في غضون أيام قليلة.
Grandma.
الجدة.
I really want him to come to our world.
أنا حقا أريده أن يأتي إلى عالمنا.
I know it's a selfish thought.
أعلم أنها فكرة أنانية.
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
he's a king.
إنه ملك.
He needs to think about
يحتاج إلى التفكير فيه
his people.
شعبه.
So,
لذا،
we probably won't see each other again.
ربما لن نرى بعضنا البعض مرة أخرى.
You can go to his world.
يمكنك الذهاب إلى عالمه.
What's the big deal?
ما هي الصفقة الكبيرة؟
I came all the way here
جئت على طول الطريق هنا
for your grandpa.
لجدك.
No.
رقم.
I can't leave you on your own.
لا أستطيع أن أتركك بمفردك.
I won't hold you back.
لن أعيقك.
I'm all alone after all.
أنا وحيد بعد كل شيء.
If you don't mind,
إن لم يكن لديك مانع،
I can go to his world too.
يمكنني الذهاب إلى عالمه أيضًا.
Then we can all be together.
ثم يمكننا أن نكون جميعًا معًا.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Have I ever lied to you?
هل كذبت عليك من قبل؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What's it like
كيف تبدو
over there?
هناك؟
The sky over there is very blue,
السماء هناك زرقاء جدا ،
the air is fresh,
الهواء نقي
and the sunshine is very cozy.
وأشعة الشمس دافئة للغاية.
Their soil is good too.
تربتهم جيدة أيضًا.
I've never seen a scallion that big.
لم أر قط بصلًا بهذا الحجم.
The fruits are sweet.
الثمار حلوة.
The flowers smell nice.
رائحة الزهور جميلة.
How great.
كم رائع.
Grandma.
الجدة.
When we get there,
عندما نصل إلى هناك،
you can keep working on fields.
يمكنك الاستمرار في العمل في الحقول.
You can plant whatever you want.
يمكنك زرع ما تريد.
They have a large field.
لديهم مجال كبير.
Sounds great.
يبدو عظيما.
I wonder
انا اتعجب
what Liangliang is doing now.
ما يفعله Liangliang الآن.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
You started without me?
هل بدأت بدوني؟
Leave that.
اترك هذا.
Let's drink this.
دعونا نشرب هذا.
Have you decided?
هل قررت؟
What will you do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm going to her world.
انا ذاهب الى عالمها.
You are coming to our world?
أنت قادم إلى عالمنا؟
Then what about your people?
ثم ماذا عن شعبك؟
I'm thinking about
أنا أفكر ب
leaving the throne to Lord Xu.
ترك العرش للورد شو.
Lord Xu?
اللورد شو؟
You haven't seen him for so long.
أنت لم تره منذ فترة طويلة.
How do you know he's still the one you knew?
كيف تعرف أنه لا يزال الشخص الذي تعرفه؟
Listen to my story.
استمع إلى قصتي.
I had a secretary surnamed Hao.
كان لدي سكرتيرة لقبها هاو.
Right?
حق؟
He's been with me ever since I started the business.
لقد كان معي منذ أن بدأت العمل.
We went through everything together.
مررنا بكل شيء معًا.
We laughed and cried together.
ضحكنا وبكينا معا.
I even gave him half of my shares.
حتى أنني أعطيته نصف أسهمي.
And guess what?
وتخيل ماذا؟
I've been away for just three months,
لقد كنت بعيدًا منذ ثلاثة أشهر فقط ،
and he took all my money and ran away.
وأخذ كل أموالي وهرب.
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
I don't want to hear your story.
لا أريد أن أسمع قصتك.
I've made my decision.
لقد اتخذت قراري.
I love Liangliang.
أنا أحب Liangliang.
I'll be
سأكون
wherever she is.
أينما كانت.
You would do anything just for love?
هل ستفعل أي شيء من أجل الحب فقط؟
You are no better than me.
انت لست افضل مني
I...
أنا...
I'm a general in your world.
أنا جنرال في عالمك.
And here you are just...
وها أنت فقط ...
You are just cosplaying.
أنت فقط ترتدي ملابس تنكرية.
Cosplaying.
تأثيري.
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
♪Get close to you♪
♪ اقترب منك